question_data =[
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level &quot;Hidden Palace Zone&quot; was later reused in the iOS port of the game. ",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Super Mario Bros. was the first video game ever created.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Animals",
      "question": "Hyenas are more closely related to cats than to dogs.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario World&quot;, the rhino mini-boss, Reznor, is named after the lead singer of the band &quot;Nine Inch Nails&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Only a small percentage of the world&#039;s population is lactose intolerant.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
]
